TOMER KEREN

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

CONTACT



tomer.keren.dev@gmail.com



www.github.com/tadaboody



Israel

SKILLS

C++, Python, TS, NodeJS

VueJS, MongoDB, Pytest, LLVM, MSVC, Terraform

Git, Gitlab CI/CD, Linux, Docker

WinDBG, Windows Sysinternals

EDUCATION

Gamma - Apollo Cyber Course

Software development course with specialization on design, architecture and low level R&D

University of Haifa

BSC Computer science

2015-2019

Bachelor's in Computer science as part of the Etgar program. Specializing in computer vision, deep learning and theoretical computer science

LANGUAGES

Hebrew (Native)

English (Fluent - Lived)

PROFILE

Experienced software developer and security researcher with a 5-year background at Unit 8200. Known for being a strong team player and guick learner, bringing innovation, an open mindset, and a passion for tackling new challenges.

I Enjoy contributing back to the open source ecosystem and have reviewed and merged commits to projects such as Pytest, the Godot Game Engine, pip and more.

Outside my love for technology I have a great love for music, and study Jazz flute and Bass guitar

WORK EXPERIENCE

Senior software developer 2022-2024

Unit 8200

- Maintained a large and efficient NodeJS-based web server.
- Helped design develop and maintain a stack for keeping
- Developed a user platform in VueJS allowing adding custom user logic to the
- · Deployed the same codebase to multiple stacks and environments, including OpenShift, Kubernetes, Docker Swarm, and Docker Compose.
- Packaged and maintained services as a cross-organizational on-prem product.

Software Developer 2019-2022

Unit 8200

- Core member of a large-scale R&D project from an early stage
- Designing and developing low-level security applications for Windows in C and
- Developing large-scale system tests in Python
- Helped migrate a large project between teams, while training and ensuring appropriate tooling and technical documentation
- Created an Python obfuscation pre-processor in Python
- Designing and developing low-level security applications for Windows in Python

Software Developer 2018-2019

Glitz - Smart Fashionable Wearable Jewelry Devices

- Designed and developed a mobile application for managing a Bluetooth Low Energy devices
- · Created a backend for collecting and managing data from various social networks.